All right, now we have an idea of what changes we need to make in our code.
现在我们知道我们需要对代码做出哪些更改了
And it looks like there are four major steps.
似乎需要四大步骤
And some might be more complicated than others.
某些步骤可能比其他步骤更复杂
Because they'll effect multiple code files at once.
因为它们会同时影响到多个代码文件
All right, so how should we go about this?
该如何操作呢？
Should pick any where to start?
我们要从哪开始
And then do all those changes perfectly,
正确执行所有这些更改
before we try to run the app on our device?
然后在设备上运行下该应用？
Well, if we attempted that method we run all the steps at once and
如果我们尝试这一方法 同时执行所有步骤
then try to run the app on our device.
然后尝试在设备上运行该应用
There's a high likelihood that the app won't work for the first time and
很有可能第一次应用无法运行
would probably run into a bunch of errors and
可能会遇到各种错误
at that point it be really hard to pinpoint the root of the problem
这时候很难找到问题的根源
because we made so many changes in the files already.
因为我们已经对文件做了太多的更改
Now on the other hand if we make smaller code changes and regularly check for
另一方面 如果我们做出更小的代码改动
errors along the way by running the app on our device, we can better identify
通过在设备上运行应用定期检查是否存在错误
the lines of code that caused the error because they'll be fewer lines changed.
则更容易发现导致错误的代码行 因为更改的代码行变少了
So this incremental approach means we'll need to plan out our code changes
采用这种步进式方法意味着我们需要规划好代码更改步骤
that will allow the app to run even if the whole feature isn't done yet.
使我们能够运行应用 即使整个功能尚未完成
Now that we know that we want to do it one step at a time
现在我们已经知道要一步步地来完成这些操作
which step should we tackle first?
那么第一步该处理什么呢？
So as developers we can prioritize in a number of ways.
作为开发者 我们可以按照多种方式来排定优先级
Often we want to make the riskiest and
通常我们会首先做出风险最大 难度最高的更改
most difficult changes first because of our initial strategy doesn't work
因为如果初始策略不可行
we need to know as soon as possible, so we can rethink our strategy.
我们需要尽早知道 从而重新规划策略
So think of it as a proof of concept to make sure the we're on the right path.
可以想象成对概念的论证 确保我们的前进方向是正确的
So in our case all these steps are pretty low risk changes
对我们来说 所有这些步骤都是风险很低的更改
because we saw the Android flavor app that it's possible to display text and
因为我们在 Android Flavor 应用中看到 我们能够在列表中
images in a list.
显示文字和图片
So the other way to prioritize is based on the data that we have.
另一种安排优先级的方式是根据我们所拥有的数据来安排优先级
Right now, we don't have images from our designer.
目前设计师还没有给我们提供图片
So often once designers produce a rough design mark it might take some time for
经常设计师在画出初步草图后 可能需要一段时间
them to deliver the final images.
才能提供最终图片
Well in the meantime we as developers can get started on writing the code.
在此期间 作为开发者 我们可以开始编写代码
So to do so
为此
we'll use something called placeholder data, also known as dummy data.
我们将用到叫做占位符的数据 也称为虚拟数据
So placeholder data means coming up with temporary or
占位符数据是指临时或虚拟数据
fake data, that we can put into the app that will give us an idea
我们可以将占位符数据放入应用中 让我们大致了解下
of what it will look like when we get the real data.
在获得实际数据后应用的外观会如何
So consider it as a placeholder for real data that be coming soon.
可以将其视为即将填充进来的实际数据的占位符
So to summarize we know that we want to make these changes one at a time.
总结下 我们知道我们需要一步步地做出这些更改
And make sure we can rebuild the app and
并且确保我们可以重构该应用并在每次更改期间
run on our of device between each change if possible.
尽可能使应用在设备上能够运行
In cases where we're missing the actual data when use fake data as a placeholder
如果缺少实际数据 我们可以使用虚拟数据作为占位符
until the real data is ready.
直到实际数据可以使用了
So in our case if we don't have the final images from the designer yet
在我们的应用中 如果设计师还没有提供最终图片
we want to get as far as we can until we get completely blocked off and
我们需要尽可能往前操作 直到完全受阻
need to wait for the real data to finish implementing the feature.
并需要等待实际数据来完成该功能
All right so taking a look at this list of changes
在看完这一系列更改后
I like your help on figuring out how to prioritize which order to do these in.
请你思考下如何优先执行哪些步骤
So go ahead and assign the numbers one through four
请按照 1 2 3 4 的先后顺序
on which step you would take first, second, third, and fourth.
为每个步骤编个号